xin chao
my name is michael thiel and i am the
ceo of driving talents
we are a global
training company to help you
motivate your younger generation of
agents of employees to be more
productive and profitable
for your companies
i want to thank yen from manulife
vietnam for inviting me here to just
share a very simple message with all of
you my brothers sisters ladies and
gentlemen from vietnam you are all
leaders and i am very proud of all of
you
now
when i started my business
it was not easy
i have survived
a car accident
i have even survived
two accidents where i dislocated my left
knee
but one thing that is very important
that kept me going
is
the strategy so i'm here to share with
you three strategies on how
i recovered and i grow my business
especially during this time of kovit 19
my best wishes to all of you
number one
please
be confident
be happy that you are so much stronger
than you ever thought
how i know this
this is because the year 2020 had been
one of the most difficult year
but brothers and sisters
over in vietnam
you are still here right now you are
still meeting yet you are still with man
you like you are still doing what you do
it is because the year 2020 did not
defeat you it did not break you it
showed you how strong you are
and with the year 2021 this year happy
new year
i want you to always remember you are
strong
this year
no problem for you
number two
let's talk about customers
there is only two things i want you to
remember about customers number one
during this hard time your customers
want to know
how
caring you are towards them
i know sometimes when you call them
you are able to get the sale or not that
is not important most important is for
you to show them that you don't see your
customers
as
sales as for you to earn money only you
are seeing your customers as a friend as
a family that you are concerned of them
because when the economy recover when
the pandemic is over the first thing the
customer would think of to do business
is with you
someone whom they consider a friend and
a family
and of course talking about customer
please remember during this time
we all want to see each other i'm still
here in malaysia we have a lockdown our
cases are still very high
but it's okay
for those of you in vietnam you could
take this chance send a video to your
customer say hello to them
make sure they are able to see your face
and feel your energy feel your care and
your love
lastly the third point i want to share
with you is to become a master
of your mindset together with your team
how to become a master of your mindset
you may ask
i want you to remember this
where your attention goes
your energy will flow so put your
attention gather your team's attention
to focus on the purpose why are you
doing this business
to focus on how many lives you will all
help every day as you remind your team
as you remind yourself
about your purpose
about the goals about the lives you will
change that is how you can motivate each
other again i want to thank you yen and
also manulife vietnam for allowing me to
say hello to all of you my brand new
friends
i thought i just wanted to say thank you
i look forward to connect with all of
you yen has my number she has linkedin
she has my facebook she has my
everything contact her she's an amazing
lady
and i look forward to sharing my story
with you stories of how i met president
barack obama when he visited my training
stories on the tips i've learned from
sir richard branson on doing business
tips i've learned from tony fernandes of
airasia for those of you who may have
heard of him i look forward
to talk to all of you again
in vietnam and let me try this
tambien that's goodbye but i want to say
something else to you let me try let me
try
henga
thank you everyone
see you soon